本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
When it's cold, you can always
put on more layers of clothes,
寒い時はとにかく重ね着しまくればなんとかなるけど
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博&微信 @诸神字幕组
but when it's hot,
there's only so much you can take off.
暑い時って脱ぐにも限界あるじゃん
Thus, your only option is to go to the pool.
そしたら　もうプールに来るしかないよね
Come on!
早く出してよ
もっかい投げるね
Wait!
Wait up!
待ってよ
Though I can't swim.
泳げないけど
What'd you say?!
なんだと
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
眠たい放課後　窓から見下ろす
春風なびいて　ひと休み
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
日听
gen & AB
翻译
颜歌＆沐沐
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
眩しい世界に　片目を瞑れば
日校
小伍
校对
戚风
时轴
WEI&和路雪
压制
wedy96
映し出す景色躍りだす
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
负责人
戚风
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
頼りない口笛　青空に吹けば
足取りもちょっと軽くなる
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
騒がしい街角　イヤフォン外して
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
見上げたら遠く声がする
Let's bask in the glowing sun
さぁ陽の光浴びてゆるやかに
Ever so gently
いつもの今日が始まる
Starting another day as usual
サンシャインと居眠りする
Napping in the sunshine
心地いい場所　君の隣で
In this cozy place with you
優しく胸に響いてる
With all these feelings booming in my heart
字幕
诸神字幕组
Episode 10
Tanaka-kun's
Summer
I didn't know you couldn't swim.
泳げないとは　それでどうしてプールに来ようと思うんだ
So why did you want to come here, then?
I was surprised when you invited me,
too, since you rarely do.
珍しく田中から声をかけてきたのも驚いたが
I'll be fine.
大丈夫
I brought my partner along.
ちゃんと相棒は連れてきたから
I'll just use the water to cool down.
俺は水に浸かって涼しくなればそれでいい
That's enough for me.
I see. That inner tube looks good on you.
そうか
その浮き輪　似合うな
Ohta...
太田…
No.
無理だぞ
Don't give me that "I just had a great idea" look.
いいこと思い付いたみたいな顔をするな
Okay... I guess I'll just go with this, then.
そっか　じゃあやっぱりこれで行こっと
Wait, Tanaka!
待て　田中
You need to warm up before you get in the pool.
プールに入る前にはしっかり準備運動しないと
Loosen up your wrists and ankles,
手首足首をほぐして　ストレッチで体の筋を十分に伸ばしておけ
and give the muscles in your body a stretch.
What if your leg cramps up in the pool?
水の中で足でもつったら大変だぞ
Especially considering you can't swim.
泳げないならなおさらだ
I see your point.
言われてみれば確かに
Okay, I'll get nice and warmed u—
よし　しっかり準備運動する…
Cramp... Cramp...
つった　つった…
Are you okay, Tanaka?
大丈夫か　田中
It's dangerous to suddenly move
muscles that are normally idle.
普段怠けている筋肉をいきなり動かすのは危険だな
Guess I should stick to lifeguard duty today.
今日は監視役に徹するか　心配だ
I hope nothing happens.
Hey there, you two!
こら　そこの二人ー
No jumping in!
飛び込まないのー
You think this is a hot spring?
温泉か
You forgot your inner tube.
浮き輪忘れてるぞ
ああ　極楽　極楽
This is heaven...
I could spend the whole summer
drifting on the water like this...
このまま夏中　水の上を漂っていたい
年上なのに浮き輪使ってる
He's older than us, but he's using a inner tube!
You can't swim? How lame!
泳げないの？　だっせー
うん　泳げない
Yep, I can't swim.
But it's okay.
けどいいんだよ　これで
流されるままに流されるのが楽だから
It takes less effort to just go with the flow.
Yes, much like my life itself.
そう　俺の人生がそうであるように
I don't get it!
意味わかんねぇ
What are you talking about?
なに言ってんの
Let's just take it!
こんなもん奪ってやる
Yeah!
No... Stop...
それ
ああ　やめて…
それ　それ
Hey!
こら
Rumble
本当に泳げない人間にそういうことをするもんじゃない
Don't ever do that to someone
who really can't swim.
Rumble
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
Why are you apologizing too, Tanaka?
なぜ田中まで
My partner...
俺の相棒が…
Did it get punctured?
穴が開いたのか
やべぇ
Oh, no! What should we do?!
どうしよう
Mommy! Daddy! Help us!
お父さんお母さん助けて
Oh, this guy may look scary,
but he's as nice as an angel, so don't worry.
いや　この人　こう見えて天使のように優しいから大丈夫
You can relax.
落ち着いて
Ohta, those goggles look scary. Take them off.
太田　そのゴーグル怖いから　外しなよ
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
そうか　すまんすまん
Please, spare my life!
お願いします　命だけは
I'll do anything you want!
なんでも言うこと聞くから
Shock
Public Pool
完全にしぼんじゃった
It's completely deflated...
We're sorry.
ごめんなさい
These things happen. Don't worry about it.
まあよくあることだ　気にするな
It was admirable of you to apologize.
ちゃんと謝れてえらいぞ
But I guess you can't play
in the pool anymore, Tanaka.
しかし田中　早くも遊べなくなってしまったな
What'll you do now?
どうする
It's no problem.
ああ　大丈夫大丈夫
I'll just stand in the pool, or walk around.
水の中でじっとしてるか　適当に歩いたりとかするから
Splish splash...
チャプチャプと
Wh-What the?
な…なんだ　泳げないはずの田中が浮いている
Tanaka can't swim, yet he's floating.
And so smoothly, at that!
それもものすごく滑らかに
Could it be...
まさか…
Of course!
そうか
田中は想像を絶するほどの脱力感の持ち主
Tanaka is listless beyond imagination.
Listless
He's naturally floating
without even thinking about it
体に力が入ってなさすぎて
Buoyant
because he doesn't have an ounce
of strength in his entire body!
意識せずとも　自然に水に浮いてしまったんだ
Amazing!
すっげー
I've never seen anyone float so perfectly!
あんなキレイに浮いてる人見たことない
He's a pro floater! I wanna try!
浮きプロだ　俺もやりたい
You're amazing, Tanaka!
すごいぞ　田中
I'm getting all kinds of praise,
even though I can't swim.
泳げないのに　なんかめっちゃ褒められてる
It's scorching hot...
あつー
Maybe working both at Wac
and as a lifeguard was too much.
ワックと掛け持ちで監視員のバイトはきつかったかな
I wish I could swim, too.
私も泳ぎたいな
Hey, teach me how to do that!
兄ちゃん　俺もやり方教えて
Me, too!
俺も
A high school kid teaching
grade schoolers how to swim?
高校生くらいの子が小学生に泳ぎ教えてるのかな
How heartwarming...
微笑ましいねー
Wait, it's you two again?
って　また君らかよー
Are you trying to be ducks?
カルガモかよ　普通に泳いでー
Swim normally, would you?
That was fun!
楽しかったー
Hey, Coach, when are you coming back?
なあコーチ　今度はいつ来るの
Teach us again sometime!
また教えてよ
大丈夫　君たちはもう立派な浮きプロだ
You're fine. You kids are already pro floaters.
There's nothing more I can teach you.
俺が教えられることはもうない
Coach!
コーチ
We will work hard and continue
to live up to the title of pro floater!
俺たち　これからも浮きプロの名に恥じぬよう努力します
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
うん　頑張って
Good luck.
Avoiding an annoying task
without hurting their feelings...
相手を傷つけることなく　さらっと面倒事を回避か
You have improved, Tanaka.
腕を上げたな　田中
Bye-bye!
バイバーイ
Bye-bye.
田中　俺は今びっくりするほど体がだるくて
Tanaka...
My body feels unbelievably tired,
and I'm incredibly sleepy.
めちゃめちゃ眠いんだが
What a coincidence. Me too.
奇遇だね　俺もだよ
ちょっと休むか
Let's go rest.
I can't move a muscle,
and I don't want to do anything.
一歩も動けないし　何もしたくないな
I feel like I've turned into Tanaka.
まるで俺まで田中になった気分だ
Huh? Then who's going to carry me home today?
じゃあ今日　誰が俺を抱えて連れて帰ってくれるの
There's nothing you can do
but wait for a new me to appear.
新たなる俺の登場を待つしかないなぁ
Mister pro floater!
浮きプロの兄ちゃん
Coach!
コーチ
Oh, the kids from before...
ああ　この前の
We meet again.
また会ったな
Hey, guess what! That thing is really
popular at our school right now!
あのなあのな　今学校でアレすっげぇ流行ってるんだぜ
Everyone says it's super fun!
みんな超楽しいって
That thing?
アレ？
You guys are doing that during your swim class?
アレをやってるのか　授業中に
See ya!
じゃあねー
太田　俺　余計なことしちゃったかな
Ohta, maybe I did something I shouldn't have...
Now I'm worried about the future
of competitive swimming.
水泳界の未来が心配
You never know what will catch on these days.
世の中　何が流行るかわからんからな
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
I seek your guidance, Master!
ご教示願います　師匠
背を１０センチ以上伸ばしたいのです　５日以内に
I wish to grow at least ten centimeters
taller within five days!
お引き取りください　無茶ぶりにもほどがある
I must ask you to leave.
You're beyond unreasonable.
Miyano, just calm down.
宮野　とにかく落ち着け
Low Fat Milk
Milk
What brought this on all of a sudden?
ほんとにどうしたの　急に
Well, Ecchan invited me
実はえっちゃんが誘ってくれて
to go see the fireworks show
in yukatas next Saturday.
次の土曜日　浴衣で花火大会へ行くことになったのですよ
Let's go, Myaano!
行こうぜ　みゃーの
'Sup!
ちょいーっす
Ecchan in a yukata...
えっちゃんの浴衣姿
Hey there...
ありんす
I'm sure she'll look very mature and beautiful!
きっととても大人っぽくて素敵なはずです
I know I don't need to act more mature
than I really am to be with her anymore,
もう無理に合わせて大人ぶる必要はないとわかってはいるのですが
but since I'll be standing next to her,
やはり隣に並ぶからには
I would like to look somewhat sexy, too.
私もそれなりにセクシーな佇まいでありたいものでして
けどこの身長では
But at my height,
せいぜいお子様用キャラクター浴衣ぐらいしか似合う気がせず
I think I'll only look good in a children's
yukata with cartoon characters on it...
Yay! I wanna scoop goldfish!
わーい　金魚すくいしたいです
I feel bad for thinking it,
but she'd probably look perfect in that.
申し訳ないが　すごく着こなせそうな気がする
I'd be like the complete opposite of sexy...
セクシーとは程遠いです
But thinking about it realistically,
しかし現実的に考えて　５日で１０センチ背を伸ばすのは難しいと思うぞ
it's not going to be easy to grow
ten centimeters in five days.
I see...
そうですか
I thought we humans could do anything
we wanted if we tried hard enough.
人間頑張れば何事もなんとかなると思ったのですが
How about asking Echizen to wear
a cartoon character yukata, too?
逆に越前にもキャラクター浴衣を着てもらったらどうだ
She likes cute stuff, after all.
あいつ　かわいい物好きだし
It'd be nice to match,
but that option is out of the question!
お揃いは嬉しいけど　その選択肢が一番なしです
We'd look like a pair of weirdos!
ただの怪しい二人組です
ていうか　そんなに悩まなくても
I don't think you need to worry so much.
すっごく簡単な解決方法があるじゃん
There's a very simple solution.
What is it, Master? Please enlighten me!
なんですか師匠　教えてください
Don't go to the fireworks show.
花火大会に行かない
That's something you should watch
live on TV, in an air-conditioned room.
ていうか　クーラーのきいた部屋でテレビ中継で見るもんでしょ　アレ
ほんとです　そもそも行かなければ浴衣を着る必要もないです
That's true!
If I don't go in the first place,
I won't need to wear a yukata!
You're a genius, Master!
天才ですか　師匠
You'll make Echizen cry.
越前泣くぞ　それ
Shouldn't you start by looking for
身長どうこうじゃなく
a yukata that'll look good on you,
regardless of your height?
まずは自分に合う浴衣を探してみた方がいいんじゃないか
There are plenty of sizes to choose from nowadays,
最近はサイズ展開が豊富だし
so you'll probably find yukatas both big and small.
浴衣も大きいのから小さいのまで　あるかもしれんぞ
Good point!
確かにです
言われてみれば　肝心の浴衣をまだチェックしていませんでした
Now that you mention it,
I haven't actually checked out any yukatas yet.
If I go to a specialty shop,
専門店に行けば　私にも似合う大人の浴衣が待っているかもしれませんね
they might have a mature-looking
yukata for me, too.
よーし　善は急げです
Okay! I must strike while the iron is hot!
早速今日の放課後　呉服屋さんへ行ってみましょう
I'll go to the kimono shop after school today!
Could you two come with me, please?
お二人とも　付き合っていただけますか
Me, too?
俺も？
別に構わんが　付き添いが男二人で大丈夫か
I don't mind, but are you sure
you want two guys along?
参考人として役に立てるかわからんぞ
I'm not sure how much help we'll be.
D-Do you think people will
see me as a two-timing harlot?
ま…まるで二股をかけている悪い女に見えちゃいますかね　私
The scent of a dangerous woman...
危険な大人の香りです
No, we don't smell it at all.
いや　香ってないから　その心配はまったくないから
There's no need for you to worry about that.
Oh, yeah! Shiraishi-san!
そうだ　白石さん
Miyano-san? What is it?
宮野さん　どうしたの
If you'd like, could you come with us, too?
よかったら　白石さんも付き合っていただけませんか
Wow... I didn't realize yukatas came
in so many shapes and sizes. Amazing.
こんなに浴衣あるんだ　すごいね
It won't be easy to choose...
迷っちゃいますね
Let's do our best to find a perfect yukata for you!
頑張って　似合う浴衣探そうね
It's reassuring to have Shiraishi's help.
白石がいるなら　心強いな
She seems very reliable.
頼りになりそう
Y-Yeah, I'll try my best!
頑張る
There are so many cute designs!
可愛いのいっぱいあるね
So people really do wear yukatas
そっか　やっぱり花火見に行くなら　浴衣とか着たりするもんなんだ
when they go to see fireworks...
私も買おうかなぁ
Maybe I should buy one, too.
Huh? Shiraishi-san, you don't wear a yukata?
あれ　白石さん　浴衣とか着ない派でしたか
No, for various reasons,
うん　いろいろあって
fireworks were always something I watched
live on TV alone at home up to now.
今までは花火イコール部屋で一人でテレビ中継で見るものだったから
In my loungewear...
部屋着で
You don't even go to see the show in person?
現場にすら行かない派でしたか　師匠と一緒です
You're the same as Master!
The same as Tanaka-kun?
田中くんと？
You two would get along well!
気が合いますね
Master, Master! I've made a discovery!
師匠　師匠　大発見です
What is it, Miyano?
どうした　宮野
When I wear geta, I'm a little taller than usual!
下駄を履くと　いつもよりちょっと背が高くなります
おお　ほんとだ
You're right.
I'm so happy!
嬉しいです
だったら　こっちの方が高さ稼げそう
In that case, you'd be even taller in these.
Th-They're like high platform shoes!
すっ　すっごく厚底です
それなら余裕でプラス１０センチです
Those would easily add ten centimeters!
Then these would definitely
add twenty centimeters!
それならこっちの方がプラス２０センチは確実だ
Sorry, but no.
それはさすがに嫌です
They have men's yukatas, too.
男物の浴衣も売ってるんだ
I bet Tanaka-kun would look good in one.
田中くん　似合いそう
I know! Shiraishi-san, do you want
to come see the fireworks with us?
そうだ　白石さんも一緒に行きませんか　花火
I want to introduce you to Ecchan, too!
えっちゃんにも紹介したいですし
You're free too, right, Master and Ohta-kun?
師匠も太田くんも暇ですよね
せっかくだから　みんなで行きましょう
We should all go together!
I'm down. Sounds fun.
いいな　楽しそうだな
Really? I'd rather stay home and sleep all day...
俺は部屋で寝てたい
So you two don't have any plans? It's decided, then!
特にご予定なしということですね　決定です
Sorry, Miyano-san...
ごめん　宮野さん
実はもう私　きっちゃんとみよちゃんが誘ってくれてて
The truth is, Kicchan and
Miyo-chan invited me already,
so I can't go with you.
Enjoy yourself without me, okay?
一緒に行けない　楽しんできてね
Seriously, thank you! Don't worry about me.
ほんとありがとう　気にしないで
Well, I guess we should buy yukatas, too.
よし　じゃあ俺たちも浴衣買うか
Let's enjoy our Japanese summer.
日本の夏を満喫するぞ
I should've made up some
fictitious plan for that day.
架空の予定を入れとけばよかった
Split into
two pieces,
so you can
wear them like
regular clothes!
Split into
two pieces,
so you can
wear them like
regular clothes!
Separated Yukata
Just insert the bow!
One
Snap
Obi
One
Snap
Obi
I like this kind. It looks easy to put on.
俺　これがいいな
着るの楽そう
This looks like something that
was made especially for you.
まるで田中のために作られたかのような商品だな
But it seems they only have
women's yukatas in this style.
けどこれ　女物しかなさそうだぞ
どう見ても可愛いな
These are way too cute for a guy.
I see... Then I guess I'll have to compromise,
そっか　じゃあ仕方ない
and wear a women's—
女物で妥協しよう
Wait, Tanaka.
待て　田中
That's the one thing you
should never compromise on.
そこは一番　妥協しちゃいかんところだ
I prefer
Effortlessness
over color
and pattern
Master! We're going to try
these on, so please wait here!
師匠　ちょっと試着してくるので　待っててください
I'm glad they both found something they liked.
二人ともいいのあったみたいでよかったね
Yeah.
ああ　宮野の身長の件も下駄でなんとかなりそうだしな
Sounds like Miyano's height issue
can be solved with a pair of geta, too.
I-I kinda feel bad for trying on a yukata, too,
み…宮野さんの浴衣探しに来たのに
when we're here to find one for Miyano-san...
なんか私まで試着とかしちゃって
あの…その…
Um... I...
Is that you, Shiraishi?!
白石か
Your hairstyle's so different, I didn't recognize you!
髪型違うから　一瞬誰かと思ったぞ
いつもと雰囲気違う
You do look quite different.
Ah, yeah. They put it up loosely for me.
うん　軽くだけど　まとめてもらっちゃった
うん　いいと思う
I like it.
It looks very good on you.
すごく似合ってる
Th-Thanks!
あ…ありがとう
嬉しい
I'm so happy! I don't care anymore!
もういい　一緒に花火行けなくてもこれで十分だよ
Even if I can't go with them, this is enough for me!
Thank you so much, Miyano-san!
ありがとう　宮野さん
No pair of geta can save that!
下駄でなんとかなるレベルじゃなかった
だ…大丈夫だ　宮野
D-Don't worry, Miyano.
You still have time. Chin up.
時間はまだある　そんなに落ち込むな
No, I'm fine...
いえ　大丈夫です
What concerns me more is that
Shiraishi-san's boobs are so big,
そんなことより　白石さんのおっぱいがすごくて
Boing
I'm losing my will to live...
もう生きてゆく自信が…
M-Miyano-san?!
み…宮野さん
Huh...
Sigh...
That was the smallest size they had.
あれでも　一番ちっさいサイズらしいです
Well, I did all I could and it didn't
work out, so I guess that's that!
まっ　やるだけやってみてダメだったので　しょうがないですね
I'll go to the fireworks show
in a cute summer dress!
花火大会は可愛い夏のワンピースで挑みます
Yeah, that should feel much cooler, too.
うん　それも涼しげでいいと思うぞ
Cheer up.
ドンマイ
She says that, but I'm sure Miyano-san
あんなこと言ってるけど
ほんとは宮野さんだって　浴衣で花火大会行きたいはずだよね
wants to go to the fireworks
show wearing a yukata, too.
She's always helping me,
いつも助けてもらってばかりだし　今度は私がなんとかしてあげたい
so I want to do something for her this time...
宮野さん　大丈夫
Miyano-san, don't worry!
If you can't find one that fits you,
we'll just make one!
既製品で合うのがないなら　作っちゃえばいいんだよ
Sh-Shiraishi-san, you can make a yukata?!
しし…白石さん　浴衣作れるんですか
浴衣は作ったことないけど　お裁縫は得意だから大丈夫
I've never made a yukata before...
But I'm good at sewing, so I'll make it work!
嬉しいです　ありがとうございます
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
頑張るよ
I'll do my best!
Isn't that great?
よかったね
Good for you.
よかったな
Good thing I recklessly trained in all kinds
of things for my high school debut...
高校デビューのために　何でも我武者羅に特訓しといてよかった
Making
sweets
PC
Sewing
Self-
improvement
Okay, let's pick out a fabric together.
じゃあ　どんな柄がいいか一緒に選ぼう
All right!
はい
I like floral patterns!
私　お花の柄がいいです
That would look great on you!
きっと似合うよ
How about this one?
こんなのはどうかな
Wow! It's beautiful!
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
素敵です
Yeah, I'm sure it'll be cute!
うん　きっと可愛い
So many food stalls...
屋台がたくさん出てるな
So many people, too.
人も多いよ
Master! Ohta-kun!
師匠　太田くん
Sorry to keep you waiting!
お待たせしました
おお　宮野か
Wow, is that you, Miyano?
It's perfect. The fit is just right.
ばっちりじゃん　ちゃんと着れてる
Yes! All thanks to Shiraishi-san!
はい　白石さんのおかげです
So not only can she make macarons,
but yukatas too.
マカロンだけでなく　浴衣まで作れるとは
I have a new-found respect for her now.
また一つ　白石への尊敬度が上がったな
I've always hated being short,
私　昔から背が低いのやだなってずっと思ってたんですけど
but this time, it's thanks to my
short stature that I get to have
でも今回は  そのおかげで
世界に一つのこんな素敵な浴衣を作ってもらうことができました
a one-of-a-kind, gorgeous yukata like this.
Sometimes, being short isn't so bad!
ちっちゃいのも　たまには悪くないですね
Yep.
I just imagined your head on Ohta's body,
今　太田の体に宮野さんの顔を嵌めた姿を想像してみたけど
but it didn't look good at all.
ぜんぜん似合わなかったから
You should stay the way you are, Miyano-san.
やっぱり宮野さんはそのままでいいよ
What were you imagining?
どんな想像したんだ
I-I don't intend to grow that tall!
そ…そこまで成長する気はないです
100 Yen
Ramune
Frankfurter
Grilled Squid
600 Yen
Ecchan! Over here!
えっちゃん　こっちです
み…みゃーの　天使か　天使なのか
Myaano! An angel?! Are you an angel?!
おダンゴ可愛すぎるぞ　こら
The buns are so cute, darn it!
Ecchan, I can't breathe...
えっちゃん　苦しいよ
What the... You two came
to see the fireworks together?
何お前ら  男二人で花火かよ
しかも浴衣まで着て  デートか
And you're even wearing yukatas?
Are you on a date?
いや　俺たちも同行者なんだが　聞いてないのか
No, we're here with you guys. You didn't hear?
'Sup!
ちょいーっす
Sorry, Echizen-san...
越前さん　ごめん
Hey there...
ありんす
You're wearing that more neatly than I expected.
意外にきっちり着てた
You guys are tagging along?
お前らも一緒なのか
たまには　みんなでワイワイするのもいいかなって思って誘ったんだよ
I thought it'd be fun to hang out as a group
once in a while, so I invited them!
All right, I guess.
しゃーねぇな
みゃーのの可愛さに免じて　今回は許可してやるか
I'll allow it this time,
on account of how cute Myaano looks.
You look much cuter, Ecchan!
えっちゃんの方が可愛いよ
Ohta is tall and has a strong physique,
太田って　背高いし　ガタイもいいし　結構似合ってんな
so he looks good in a yukata.
Come to think of it, we used to go
to the summer festival together as kids.
そういや　ちっさい頃は一緒にお祭り来たりしたっけ
Ohta's ma made us matching yukatas.
太田のおふくろさんがお揃いの浴衣作ってくれて
懐かしいな
Brings back memories...
Echizen, I just remembered how
越前
そういえば　子供の頃はよく一緒に来てたな　夏祭り
we used to go to the summer festival
together when we were kids,
お揃いの浴衣を着て
in our matching yukatas.
Huh?! I-I don't remember that!
お…覚えてねぇよ
Wh-What? Don't glare at me...
な…なんだよ　ガン飛ばしてんじゃねぇぞ
That's really cute. You look good, Echizen.
可愛いな　よく似合ってるぞ　越前
Wh-Wh-What is he saying outta the blue?!
なな…何言ってんのこいつは　突然
Y-You look better in your yukata
than you did back then, too...
お…お前も　昔より似合ってんじゃん　浴衣
太田　かき氷　シロップ練乳かけ放題だって
Ohta, they say you can put as much condensed
milk syrup on the shaved ice as you want.
What'd you say?! There is a God!
なんだと　神か
Shaved
Ice
Shaved Ice
Unlimited Syrup
Should I go with the classic strawberry milk?
やっぱり定番のイチゴミルクか
But mango sounds good, too...
しかし　マンゴーも捨て難い
太田　知ってるか
Ohta...
Have you heard?
There's this trend called "shaved ice shampoo."
今　巷じゃ「かき氷シャンプー」ってのが流行ってるんだぜ
This will cool you off, idiot!
お前なんかひんやりしてろ　バーカー
Ecchan?!
えっちゃん
It went down my back...
Oh, good.
よかった　いつもの越前さんだ
背中に…
Echizen-san is back to her normal self.
So cold...
寒い
It's starting!
始まりました
It's magnificent.
見事だな
Yeah, it is.
おお　そうだな
I should've bought the Tengu geta!
天狗の下駄　買っておけばよかったです
I take it back! I hate being short!
やっぱりちっちゃいのは嫌ですー
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
BON-BON　いつもの　いたずら猫みたい
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
自然体で　ワガママしたい
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
気ままミュージック　こっそりノリノリで
空想なら得意かも
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
いわゆる幸せ　それってなぁに？
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
好きなこと　とことん　やってみて
わかるのかなぁ
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
BON-BON　ドラマチック
I want to put my life into its hands
「そこそこ」が希望
ポジティブチケット　持ってたいね
Maybe a positive attitude is better
精一杯なら　正解なのかな
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
ポーカーフェイスは苦手です
Everyday life makes me dizzy
グルグルしちゃうね
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
My dear listlessness
Once more
もう一回
My dear listlessness
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
Will it be a table for one, sir?
一名様でございますか
Ohhhtaaa...
太…田…
He was wearing underwear!
パンツははいてた　パンツははいてたから
...to save you!
助けに行くからな
Eyelid eyes!
まぶた目だー
次回　第１１話「田中くんの文化祭」
Next time, Episode 11:
Next Episode
Tanaka-kun's Cul...
Tanaka-kun's Cultural Festival.